var title = 'Traduza para grego.';

var questions = [

 {
   prompt: "eu",
   answer: ["εγώ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "tu",
   answer: ["εσύ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "ele",
   answer: ["αυτός", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "ela",
   answer: ["αυτή", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "isso",
   answer: ["αυτό", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "nós",
   answer: ["εμείς", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "vós",
   answer: ["εσείς", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "eles",
   answer: ["αυτοί", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "elas",
   answer: ["αυτές", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "esses",
   answer: ["αυτά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

];